[{"answer": " Y", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Mmm  I'm gonna remember that if I'm ever in that place", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What happens if the husband dies after the wife, who brings in the clothing in then", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Yes I suppose they do", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Tonight", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Uh oh I don't think we think we can make it tonight,  we have plans", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Uh oh I don't think we think we can make it tonight,  we have plans", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " We have plans", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Maybe he was just trying to be nice", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Maybe", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Why wouldn't they like us?  Again with the pepper? What do you gotta use all the pepper for", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Ya, we've been trying to reunite my friend with his father who lives in that place. But he's afraid to fly alone, you know he's kinda withdrawn, but he seems to take to you.  So it's a perfect solution", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "And you'll send me a postcard. ", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No I haven't seen it yet", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'm goin", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Nobody died. Jack I want you to do me a big favor.  In my garage there are a couple of boxes", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'm gonna explain what boxes", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Ok, see you later", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What show", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yea", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Oh hi my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "My idiot son could open that garage door", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Just do it first thing tomorrow. I need it.", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Ya that was some list", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " The black and white", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "That's righ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You're right he's ripping me of", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Ya so have ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You don't think it's fair", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No no, I found the place, I set the whole thing up, I'm doing all the leg work", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh, there's leg work", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yes, he's insane, that's what I think", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I don't know, I don't know what to do.  Oh god.... so how was the movie", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I don't know, I don't know what to do.  Oh god.... so how was the movie", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Ya what do you mean from what you saw", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Uh from what I saw it was pretty good", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Well I um I didn't ah actually get to see the whole movie", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Yea why not", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " You were making, out during my friend's List", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " We're both living with our parents", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "No I don't think so. I saw my friend as I was leaving but see me", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "We have to make the flight, we're with a charter group. If we don't the trip is off", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Some place else? What about that place", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You know, I was thinking today. I never liked those Seinfelds anyway, he's an idiot all together.  Ah there's my friend.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Hell", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "What happens to charter tickets when you don't use em", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Yes I suppose they are", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I'm the father", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "He said I was dead", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Ok.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Bye.", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "my friend? my friend are you ok", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "You did enough", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": " Pair of bear claws please", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " Hello my friend", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Say, I happened to catch you coming out of my friend's List the other night", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Yes I was", "qsentId": 58}]